(Howard:)Okay, Sheldon,
what was it supposed to be?
(Howard:)Fine, it's out of the washer.
(Howard:)I'll call you when it's in the dryer.
All right, let's go.
[CLEARING THROAT]
[PENNY SIGHING]
- What do you think?
- Um, that one.
- Because of the additional Ethernet ports?
- Sure.
(Sheldon:)He doesn't need them.
He's got a six-port Ethernet switch.
- Oh, okay, then this one.
- Why?
(Howard:)I don't know.
The man on the box looks so happy.
Penny, if I'm going to buy Leonard a gift,
I'm going to do it right.
(Sheldon:)I refuse to let him experience
the same childhood trauma I did.
I know I'm gonna regret this,
but what trauma?
On my 12th birthday,
I really wanted a titanium centrifuge...
(Sheldon:)...so, you know,
I could separate radioactive isotopes.
Of course, yeah.
(Sheldon:)Instead of a titanium centrifuge,
my parents bought me...